Hello everyone, welcome back to to this another tutorial topic. So today we will create my
skill point key constant or the MySQL, which is the essential feature of establishing relationship
between table in the database. Okay, so first of all simply just explain for the point key
constant in the MySQL is to link to table stability based on the relationships between their
column and you can choose the differential integrity by imposing a link between the values in
the two column. Okay, so first of all I can go for the first table and the first table the customer
table and here I have already equated this customer table information for the data query and this
comment is completely successful. Okay, so because first I conclude the id and the name page
address survey and the primary key for the id. Okay, now here I'll create another table for order
table and they are creating for the id date and also the customer study and here I can create for the
constraints for the point key customer then the point key the customer study and the reference for
the customer is specific for the id column. Okay, and here I can also put them on then also the
primary key is id. Okay, and the table is completely successfully created. Okay, so here I have
completely created these two tables first on the customer and the order. Okay, and now in this
two table just here add the point key constant the column for the customer id the reference also
here the customer id and the customer table I have shown the statement over the perfect label.
Okay, so now it is perfectly created and now here is the completely created two table and now
just here I can define for the quantity constant on the existing column. Okay, so here I suppose
some example for the customer and the order table have already been created in the MySQL database. Okay,
and now just we can add the quantity constant on the id column on the order table. Okay,
so now the first of all we can start this outer for the table. Okay, so the point for that
going on table is like the order and then going to the next depend here just create add the
constant for the fk means the point key and underscore the orders. Okay, and the next step here
I can also create for for i so fra i gn so this is the foreign key and in this inside I can
define for this specific column for dining. Okay, and now you have also created the reference so
this is the reference for here called the customers. Okay, so if the customers for the specific column
suppose like for this specific column for dining. Okay, so now we can simply create for this
query and in this query just add the foreign constant on the column on the existing table. Okay,
so now just select all the data query and now just execute and just run and you can see
that comment is completely successful. Okay, so now just go for here and look for the new query
or just here type for so first of all here type this select then the cluster from here is called
the customer table and also for the in this try for select the cluster from the order table. Okay,
so now here the two table both for the program you can see here perfectly created the first one i
d name page address and the customer table and the table or id customer id and this is the order
table. Okay, so here completely verify this is statement. Okay, and now here I have also created
the dropping this the point table okay. So now here first of all I will use the MySQL query to drop
the quantity constant for the column of the table okay. So first of all here I can create for these
just go to here and type for here the outer table for the outer table okay, so here I can also create
just go for here this is the order stable and just type for here the drop statement for the
this is the fine key and just type for it the underscore this is the order statement okay.
So now it will define perfectly and just simply just type include and perfectly select and now
just click and you can see this stuff fine is directly not defined okay. So here this is completely
not defined requirement where it will give errors. So now here we can completely create these
statements of suppose the error first of all define and here simply just remove from here the
customer stable so just here I can first of all here at this end this is the drop statement
here the drop JV drop customers okay. So define this perfectly and now just I can select all
and you can inside customer becomes reference to the fine key constant. So here this is
create this drop table customer okay. So here in this session I use the completely created the
orders data and give the fine key customer and look for the reference for the customer. So
okay and here then there's a review for the fine key constant in my skill and here I have
completely used a practical example so I hope you perfectly understand to the session so thank
Thank you for watching and happy coding.